<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Descriptor Specification on Lifecycle Manager Learning Center</title><link>https://pages.github.ibm.com/TNC/alm-docs.github.io/reference/descriptor-specification/</link><description>Recent content in Descriptor Specification on Lifecycle Manager Learning Center</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://pages.github.ibm.com/TNC/alm-docs.github.io/reference/descriptor-specification/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Assembly Descriptor</title><link>https://pages.github.ibm.com/TNC/alm-docs.github.io/reference/descriptor-specification/assembly-descriptor/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://pages.github.ibm.com/TNC/alm-docs.github.io/reference/descriptor-specification/assembly-descriptor/</guid><description>Introduction This document describes the assembly descriptors that are used by the Agile Lifecycle Manager (ALM). ALM needs to have descriptions of the building blocks of applications that it is going to manage. The basic building blocks are described in resource descriptors (resource descriptors are described in separate document). Sets of these are composed into assembly descriptors to allow designers to describe a complete application/service that they need LM to manage.</description></item><item><title>Resource Descriptor</title><link>https://pages.github.ibm.com/TNC/alm-docs.github.io/reference/descriptor-specification/resource-descriptor/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://pages.github.ibm.com/TNC/alm-docs.github.io/reference/descriptor-specification/resource-descriptor/</guid><description>Introduction This document describes the descriptors that are used by the Agile Lifecycle Manager (ALM). ALM needs to have descriptions of the building blocks of applications that it is going to manage. The basic building blocks are described in resource descriptors. Sets of these are composed into assembly descriptors to allow designers to describe a complete application/service that they need LM to manage.
Naming Each resource must have a name and a version - it is advisable to name the resource assuming other people might use the same name i.</description></item><item><title>Relationship State</title><link>https://pages.github.ibm.com/TNC/alm-docs.github.io/reference/descriptor-specification/relationship-state/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://pages.github.ibm.com/TNC/alm-docs.github.io/reference/descriptor-specification/relationship-state/</guid><description>Relationship State When defining a relationship we must also define when this relationship should be created and deleted (ceased) within the context of the assembly lifecycle (and the lifecycles of its components)
This is achieved by specifying the minimum state each end of the relationship must occupy for the relationship to exist The target component is the driving end of the relationship, meaning that the relationship will be created when the target component will reach its minimum state in this transition In addition to specifying the minimum state, we can also define a modifier for the state which identifies whether the relationship should be created before (pre) or after (post) the relevant end transitions</description></item></channel></rss>