<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Lifecycle Manager API on Telco Network Cloud Orchestration Learning Center</title><link>https://ibm.github.io/telco-network-cloud-drivers/reference/lm-api/</link><description>Recent content in Lifecycle Manager API on Telco Network Cloud Orchestration Learning Center</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://ibm.github.io/telco-network-cloud-drivers/reference/lm-api/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Interface Architecture</title><link>https://ibm.github.io/telco-network-cloud-drivers/reference/lm-api/interface-architecture/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ibm.github.io/telco-network-cloud-drivers/reference/lm-api/interface-architecture/</guid><description>The Telco Network Cloud Orchestration (TNCO) API is responsible for interactions with the operations available from TNCO.
API Interaction Principles Each of the major components within TNCO have been built as micro-services using HTTP as the transport mechanism for requests and responses.
The TNCO API uses a combination of REST style interfaces and RPC interfaces.
The RPC-style interface is used to submit Intents to TNCO. All other interfaces use a REST-style.</description></item><item><title>Sequence</title><link>https://ibm.github.io/telco-network-cloud-drivers/reference/lm-api/scenarios/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ibm.github.io/telco-network-cloud-drivers/reference/lm-api/scenarios/</guid><description>Resource Manager Handling Resource Manager Onboarding When a resource manager is onboarded, Telco Network Cloud Orchestration (TNCO) invokes a set of calls to the Resource Manager detailed in the Resource Manager API document.
Delete Resource Manager Get Resource Manager Details Update Resource Manager The resource manager returns the details of the resources and locations, and TNCO will store any new details. TNCO will not remove any existing details.
Assembly Creation and State Transition Healing Scaling Scale Out ​ ScaleIn ​ Topology Requests</description></item></channel></rss>