<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Configuration on Telco Network Cloud Orchestration Learning Center</title><link>https://ibm.github.io/telco-network-cloud-drivers/installation/lm/production/configuration/</link><description>Recent content in Configuration on Telco Network Cloud Orchestration Learning Center</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://ibm.github.io/telco-network-cloud-drivers/installation/lm/production/configuration/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Access Configuration</title><link>https://ibm.github.io/telco-network-cloud-drivers/installation/lm/production/configuration/access-config/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ibm.github.io/telco-network-cloud-drivers/installation/lm/production/configuration/access-config/</guid><description>Configuring Access to Agile Lifecycle Manager (ALM) The installation of ALM includes an Ingress Controller which exposes the key services externally. This needs to be configured so that access to these services will be on the required hostnames and ports.
If your environment already has an Ingress Controller available, then disable the one that comes with the LM installation. You can check the status of your ingress controller with:
kubectl get service --all-namespaces | grep ingress</description></item><item><title>Sizing</title><link>https://ibm.github.io/telco-network-cloud-drivers/installation/lm/production/configuration/sizing/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ibm.github.io/telco-network-cloud-drivers/installation/lm/production/configuration/sizing/</guid><description>Configuring Sizing of Agile Lifecycle Manager (ALM) The default install of LM makes use of the default settings, which will deploy the Standard flavour of LM. This includes:
single instance of Foundation services execution of the LM configurator job to configure default settings single instance of ALM services, with all security features enabled Alternative Sizing Flavours The flavours directory included in the lm-helm-charts package contains helm values and other useful files for installing alternative recommended deployments of the ALM.</description></item><item><title>Security</title><link>https://ibm.github.io/telco-network-cloud-drivers/installation/lm/production/configuration/security/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ibm.github.io/telco-network-cloud-drivers/installation/lm/production/configuration/security/</guid><description>Configuring Security in Lifecycle Manager The recommended installation of Lifecycle Manager is with security enabled. This will give the following benefits:
HTTPS access to services Role-based Access Control to the Lifecycle Manager user interface Protected access to LM APIs Disabling Security The easiest way to disable security during installation is by including the No Security flavour
No Security Flavour Directory: no-security This flavour disables LM security and is intended for development/testing purposes.</description></item><item><title>Storage</title><link>https://ibm.github.io/telco-network-cloud-drivers/installation/lm/production/configuration/storage/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ibm.github.io/telco-network-cloud-drivers/installation/lm/production/configuration/storage/</guid><description>Storage Class By default, any service requiring persistence is configured to use the default provisioner of your Kubernetes cluster. You can check your default with kubectl:
kubectl get storageclass
The default storage class will be shown with (default) alongside it&amp;rsquo;s name. If you have no default, you can mark an existing class as the default with:
kubectl patch storageclass &amp;lt;your-class-name&amp;gt; -p '{&amp;quot;metadata&amp;quot;: {&amp;quot;annotations&amp;quot;:{&amp;quot;storageclass.kubernetes.io/is-default-class&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;true&amp;quot;}}}'
Alternatively, you may explicitly set the storage class for each service by adding storageClass fields into your custom values file.</description></item><item><title>External LDAP</title><link>https://ibm.github.io/telco-network-cloud-drivers/installation/lm/production/configuration/external-ldap/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ibm.github.io/telco-network-cloud-drivers/installation/lm/production/configuration/external-ldap/</guid><description>Agile Lifecycle Manager (ALM) makes use of LDAP as its user store for secure access. It is configured by default to connect to the OpenLDAP service which is part of installation. Is is possible to disable this installation of this OpenLDAP service, and to connect to an external LDAP implementation. This includes support for Active Directory.
Configuring an External LDAP Server To use an LDAP Server other than the pre-configured OpenLDAP instance which comes as part of the LM installation, follow these steps.</description></item><item><title>Scaling ALM</title><link>https://ibm.github.io/telco-network-cloud-drivers/installation/lm/production/configuration/scaling-policy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ibm.github.io/telco-network-cloud-drivers/installation/lm/production/configuration/scaling-policy/</guid><description>The following guide explains how to prepare Agile Lifecycle Manager (ALM) to scale with CPU usage.
Pre-requisites: The Kubernetes metrics server must be running in your Kubernetes environment for scaling of ALM to work. Configure ALM ALM services can be setup to scale from the point they are installed by setting some custom helm values. Each service has configurable options for resources and autoscaling thresholds.
Before running a helm install of ALM you can create a custom values file with content like the following for each service:</description></item><item><title>Install Error Links</title><link>https://ibm.github.io/telco-network-cloud-drivers/installation/lm/production/configuration/error-links-install/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ibm.github.io/telco-network-cloud-drivers/installation/lm/production/configuration/error-links-install/</guid><description>Direct links to a logging dashboard can be enabled in the Agile Lifecycle Manager (ALM) User Interface. This is an optional feature that will generate a link to a relevant search in a logging dashboard based on any error that has occurred in an assembly instance. The link displays like this:
Enabling the dashboard links during ALM installation Create a values YAML file the following content in order to enable the logging dashboard: configurator:
loggingDashboard:
enabled: true
## The domain used to connect to the logging dashboard UI
endpoint: http://kibana.</description></item></channel></rss>