<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Security on Lifecycle Manager Learning Center</title><link>https://ibm.github.io/telco-network-cloud-drivers/reference/security/</link><description>Recent content in Security on Lifecycle Manager Learning Center</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://ibm.github.io/telco-network-cloud-drivers/reference/security/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Default Client Credentials</title><link>https://ibm.github.io/telco-network-cloud-drivers/reference/security/default-client-credentials/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ibm.github.io/telco-network-cloud-drivers/reference/security/default-client-credentials/</guid><description>During the default installation of Agile Lifecycle Manager (ALM) your system is deployed with a set of credentials configured for three standard clients. Unless changed (recommended), these will be as follows;
Default Clients Client ID Secret Details LmClient pass123 Default admin client. The id and secret can be configured at installation NimrodClient pass123 Client used by the LM user interface. The secret can be configured at installation DokiClient pass123 Client used by the LM behaviour center.</description></item><item><title>Default LM Users</title><link>https://ibm.github.io/telco-network-cloud-drivers/reference/security/default-security-users/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ibm.github.io/telco-network-cloud-drivers/reference/security/default-security-users/</guid><description>The default installation of Agile Lifecycle Manager (ALM) comes with the following default users, groups, roles and privileges.
Default users Username Password Member of Group Suspended Jack jack SLMAdmin No Jill jill Portal No John john SLMAdmin No Jane jane SLMAdmin, RootSecAdmin No Derek derek RootSecAdmin No Lisa lisa - No Kim kim ReadOnly No Steve steve SLMAdmin Yes Default groups Group Name Roles Granted SLMAdmin SLMAdmin Portal Portal RootSecAdmin RootSecAdmin ReadOnly ReadOnly Default roles SLM Role Description Privileges SLM Admin A user with the &amp;lsquo;SLMAdmin&amp;rsquo; role can perform the whole range of operations permissible with ALM Network Service instances - CRUDEVNF Instances - CRUDENetwork Service Designs - CRUDEVNF Designs - CRUDEDeployment Locations - CRUDEVDUs - CRUDEBehaviour Tests - CRUDIntent Requests - Read and ExecuteResource Driver - Read and Write Portal As a user with &amp;lsquo;Portal&amp;rsquo; role can create Assembly Instances, but otherwise has read-only access Network Service instances - CRUDEVNF Instances - Read-OnlyNetwork Service Designs - Read-OnlyVNF Designs - NO ACCESSDeployment Locations - Read-OnlyVDUs - Read-OnlyBehaviour Tests - CRUDEIntent Requests - Read and ExecuteResource Driver - Read and Write ReadOnly As a user with &amp;lsquo;ReadOnly&amp;rsquo; role has read-only access to all parts of the system Network Service instances - Read-OnlyVNF Instances - Read-OnlyNetwork Service Designs - Read-OnlyVNF Designs - Read-OnlyDeployment Locations - Read-OnlyVDUs - Read-OnlyBehaviour Tests - Read-OnlyResource Driver - Read-Only RootSecAdmin &amp;lsquo;Root Security Admin&amp;rsquo;.</description></item><item><title>Configuring External LDAP Connections</title><link>https://ibm.github.io/telco-network-cloud-drivers/reference/security/configuring-external-ldap/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ibm.github.io/telco-network-cloud-drivers/reference/security/configuring-external-ldap/</guid><description>Agile Lifecycle Manager (ALM) makes use of LDAP as its user store for secure access. It is configured by default to connect to the OpenLDAP service which is part of the installation. It is possible to disable this installation of this OpenLDAP service, and to connect to an external LDAP implementation using different mechanisms including support for Active Directory.
Configuring an External LDAP Server To use an LDAP Server other than the pre-configured OpenLDAP instance which comes as part of the LM installation, follow these steps.</description></item></channel></rss>