<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Develop a Network Service Package on Lifecycle Manager Learning Center</title><link>https://pages.github.ibm.com/TNC/alm-docs.github.io/user-guides/network-service-design/develop-a-network-service-package/</link><description>Recent content in Develop a Network Service Package on Lifecycle Manager Learning Center</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://pages.github.ibm.com/TNC/alm-docs.github.io/user-guides/network-service-design/develop-a-network-service-package/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Design a Network Service</title><link>https://pages.github.ibm.com/TNC/alm-docs.github.io/user-guides/network-service-design/develop-a-network-service-package/design-a-network-service/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://pages.github.ibm.com/TNC/alm-docs.github.io/user-guides/network-service-design/develop-a-network-service-package/design-a-network-service/</guid><description>This section describes the steps to design and model a Network Service. A Network Service is typically designed prior to the implementation. This is part of a customer project in which requirements are gathered, a design is made including the Network Service Design, and then implemented.
Objectives Learn how to model a Network Service Create a Network Service graphical model that can be used during implementation Pre-requisites An understanding of the customer requirements for the Network Service in terms of composition, location, relationships, networking, testing, and underlying infrastructure requirements.</description></item><item><title>Setting up a project</title><link>https://pages.github.ibm.com/TNC/alm-docs.github.io/user-guides/network-service-design/develop-a-network-service-package/setting-up-a-project/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://pages.github.ibm.com/TNC/alm-docs.github.io/user-guides/network-service-design/develop-a-network-service-package/setting-up-a-project/</guid><description>The first step in developing a Network Service (NS) is to create a NS project.
Create NS Project On your local environment, you create a NS project by running the following LMCTL command in the folder you want the NS to be created in:
lmctl project create --name myvns --version 0.1 --servicetype NS ./myns
This creates a NS directory structure for the NS. The result of this is a NS directory structure that is created that should look like this:</description></item><item><title>Implement a Network Service</title><link>https://pages.github.ibm.com/TNC/alm-docs.github.io/user-guides/network-service-design/develop-a-network-service-package/implement-a-network-service-descriptor/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://pages.github.ibm.com/TNC/alm-docs.github.io/user-guides/network-service-design/develop-a-network-service-package/implement-a-network-service-descriptor/</guid><description>Objectives Learn how to access Service Designer tool in Agile Lifecycle Manager (ALM) Create a new Assembly Descriptor working as a starting point for a new Network Service (NS) design Design the Network Service using the Designer Pre-requisites Before you begin following pre-requisites should be fulfilled:
Access to ALM environment with applicable user role assigned to the user account (see Installation and Config of ALM for more details on user roles) Necessary Virtual Network Function (VNF) packages developed and onboarded to the ALM environment (see Develop a VNF package for more details) Used the LMCTL command to create the NS project and pushed that into the environment Create a new Assembly Descriptor This step is only relevant if you have not created a NS project with LMCTL yet and you start one from scratch in the ALM Designer UI.</description></item><item><title>Finalize a Project</title><link>https://pages.github.ibm.com/TNC/alm-docs.github.io/user-guides/network-service-design/develop-a-network-service-package/finalize-a-project/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://pages.github.ibm.com/TNC/alm-docs.github.io/user-guides/network-service-design/develop-a-network-service-package/finalize-a-project/</guid><description>At this stage, you have created your NS and behaviour tests, and you are happy with the design. You can pull the project back to your local directory before pushing it to your GIT.
Pull project to local directory If you want to pull the design you have made in the ALM UI into your local project directory run the following command:
lmctl project pull dev
This will pull all NS artifacts you created in the designer out from your ALM development installation into your local directory.</description></item></channel></rss>