<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>API Definitions on Telco Network Cloud Orchestration Learning Center</title><link>https://ibm.github.io/telco-network-cloud-drivers/reference/lm-api/api-definition/</link><description>Recent content in API Definitions on Telco Network Cloud Orchestration Learning Center</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://ibm.github.io/telco-network-cloud-drivers/reference/lm-api/api-definition/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Asynchronous State Change Events</title><link>https://ibm.github.io/telco-network-cloud-drivers/reference/lm-api/api-definition/asynchronous-state-change-events/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ibm.github.io/telco-network-cloud-drivers/reference/lm-api/api-definition/asynchronous-state-change-events/</guid><description>LM emits events when the state of an assembly and its components changes. Messages that are sent asynchronously are put onto a Kafka bus. The exact topics can be configured. These are emitted in response to Intent Requests causing the state of the Assembly Instance, or its associated components, to change. In the event of a failure to change state, an event will also be emitted.
Associated with each example is a table explaining the fields in the example.</description></item><item><title>Resource Health Events</title><link>https://ibm.github.io/telco-network-cloud-drivers/reference/lm-api/api-definition/resource-health-events/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ibm.github.io/telco-network-cloud-drivers/reference/lm-api/api-definition/resource-health-events/</guid><description>Integrity Events These events are sent to enable a resource to indicate if a resource is working or broken.
Example Integrity Metric Event {
&amp;quot;metricKey&amp;quot; : &amp;quot;142971c5-a84b-4d34-af15-435ba8640aec&amp;quot;,
&amp;quot;metricName&amp;quot; : &amp;quot;h_integrity&amp;quot;,
&amp;quot;integrity&amp;quot; : &amp;quot;OK&amp;quot;,
&amp;quot;message&amp;quot; : &amp;quot;Everything is working&amp;quot;
}
Field Details Field Description Mandatory metricKey The key given to the resource manager when the resource was created as a token to be used within these messages Yes metricName The name of the metric as defined in the resource descriptor Yes integrity A value indicating if the resource associated with the metric Key is working allowed values are “OK” for working and “BROKEN” when healing is required Yes message An optional test string to include information about the integrity of the resource.</description></item><item><title>Error Responses</title><link>https://ibm.github.io/telco-network-cloud-drivers/reference/lm-api/api-definition/error-responses/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ibm.github.io/telco-network-cloud-drivers/reference/lm-api/api-definition/error-responses/</guid><description>All the API calls described in this section will return the following information in the Response Body when an error is encountered (e.g. for a 404, 403, 500 Response Code):
{
&amp;quot;details&amp;quot;: {},
&amp;quot;localizedMessage&amp;quot;: &amp;quot;string&amp;quot;,
&amp;quot;url&amp;quot;: &amp;quot;string&amp;quot;
}
Response properties
Field Description details Any additional information related to the error that may be useful during debugging localizedMessage User-friendly description of the error that has occurred url the URL of the root cause of the problem or null if unknown</description></item></channel></rss>