<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Production on Telco Network Cloud Orchestration Learning Center</title><link>https://ibm.github.io/telco-network-cloud-drivers/installation/lm/production/</link><description>Recent content in Production on Telco Network Cloud Orchestration Learning Center</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://ibm.github.io/telco-network-cloud-drivers/installation/lm/production/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Getting Started</title><link>https://ibm.github.io/telco-network-cloud-drivers/installation/lm/production/production-start/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ibm.github.io/telco-network-cloud-drivers/installation/lm/production/production-start/</guid><description>This section details how to install Telco Network Cloud Orchestration (TNCO) using Helm on an existing Kubernetes cluster. This will install the following Helm charts:
helm-foundation - reference Helm Chart for deploying the third-party components required by TNCO. lm-configurator - Helm Chart executing a Kubernetes job to create relevant schemas and other configuration required by TNCO. lm-helm - Helm Chart for deploying the TNCO Microservices Pre-requisites Kubernetes A Kubernetes cluster is required to install TNCO.</description></item><item><title>Offline</title><link>https://ibm.github.io/telco-network-cloud-drivers/installation/lm/production/offline/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ibm.github.io/telco-network-cloud-drivers/installation/lm/production/offline/</guid><description>The following guide explains how to pre-prepare the artifacts required by Telco Network Cloud Orchestration (TNCO) during installation so you may complete installation at a later date without internet access.
Preparing Offline Install Helm Charts The Helm charts should have already been gathered and copied onto the installation machine.
Docker Images Create a workspace mkdir lm-docker-images
Identifying Images Below is a full list of the docker images used by the sub-charts in v2.</description></item><item><title>Installing TNCO</title><link>https://ibm.github.io/telco-network-cloud-drivers/installation/lm/production/install-lm/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ibm.github.io/telco-network-cloud-drivers/installation/lm/production/install-lm/</guid><description>This section assumes you have followed the configuration steps and now have:
a helm-foundation Helm chart an lm-configurator Helm chart an lm-helm - Helm chart a custom values YAML file Installing with Helm You can now install the various LM Helm charts in the order listed above, using the helm install command
helm install &amp;lt;your-helm-chart&amp;gt; --name &amp;lt;your-release-name&amp;gt; --namespace &amp;lt;your-namespace&amp;gt; -f &amp;lt;your-custom-values-file&amp;gt; -f &amp;lt;your-additional-flavour-files&amp;gt;
cicdhub-helm-chart - path to the Helm chart your-release-name - unique name used to identify this installation in Helm your-namespace - Kubernetes namespace to install into (leave out to use default).</description></item></channel></rss>