<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>CI/CD on Lifecycle Manager Learning Center</title><link>https://ibm.github.io/telco-network-cloud-drivers/user-guides/cicd/</link><description>Recent content in CI/CD on Lifecycle Manager Learning Center</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://ibm.github.io/telco-network-cloud-drivers/user-guides/cicd/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Introduction</title><link>https://ibm.github.io/telco-network-cloud-drivers/user-guides/cicd/introduction/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ibm.github.io/telco-network-cloud-drivers/user-guides/cicd/introduction/</guid><description>Pre-requisites The following links introduce terms used through out this section:
Key ALM concepts introduce the Agile Lifecycle Manager (ALM) programming model used to model VNFs and Network Services.
Assembly and resource specifications give detailed descriptions of how to model lifecycles in ALM.
Introduction Cloud DevOps best practices and principles are at the heart of the ALM solution. To scale any Cloud based networking program, a unified operations and engineering model is combined with a set of automation tools that can simplify and automate the complexities of an end-to-end VNF or Network Service lifecycle.</description></item><item><title>Getting Started</title><link>https://ibm.github.io/telco-network-cloud-drivers/user-guides/cicd/getting-started/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ibm.github.io/telco-network-cloud-drivers/user-guides/cicd/getting-started/</guid><description>Objective This section describes how to setup your own Agile Lifecycle Manager (ALM) CI/CD process and tools using the CI/CD Hub.
Pre-requisites You must have installed the CI/CD Hub software and attach one or more ALMs. A detailed description of the CI/CD Hub software can be found here.
ALM CI/CD Process and Tasks Once the CI/CD Hub is up and running, perform the following tasks to configure it to the needs of your team.</description></item><item><title>Configure the Hub</title><link>https://ibm.github.io/telco-network-cloud-drivers/user-guides/cicd/configure-cicd-hub/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ibm.github.io/telco-network-cloud-drivers/user-guides/cicd/configure-cicd-hub/</guid><description>Objectives A newly installed CI/CD Hub will require some additional configuration to setup users and cross component integrations.
Pre-requisites Newly installed CI/CD Hub See initial CI/CD Hub login details Add users to OpenLDAP To add users to the to the OpenLDAP installed with the CI/CD Hub. You can follow the instructions to add users to a standalone Agile Lifecycle Manager (ALM).
Slave ALMs can be configured at installation time to use the OpenLDAP instance deployed with the CI/CD Hub.</description></item></channel></rss>