<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Demos on Telco Network Cloud Orchestration Learning Center</title><link>https://ibm.github.io/telco-network-cloud-drivers/best-practices/demos/</link><description>Recent content in Demos on Telco Network Cloud Orchestration Learning Center</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://ibm.github.io/telco-network-cloud-drivers/best-practices/demos/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Introduction</title><link>https://ibm.github.io/telco-network-cloud-drivers/best-practices/demos/introduction/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ibm.github.io/telco-network-cloud-drivers/best-practices/demos/introduction/</guid><description>Telco Network Cloud Orchestration (TNCO) Demonstrations This section introduces a set of working TNCO demonstrations. With working code and scripted scenarios to help you get up and running quickly.
CI/CD Automated Pipeline Description: Setup and use an automated CI/CD Pipeline to automate on-boarding, test, and deployment of an example Voice Service. Key points: Automated pipeline, automated behaviour driven testing, automated environment creation, automated binary package store Link: CI/CD pipeline Coming soon Dummy EPC End to End VoIP Service NFVI Automation</description></item><item><title>CI/CD Pipeline demonstration</title><link>https://ibm.github.io/telco-network-cloud-drivers/best-practices/demos/cicd-pipeline/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ibm.github.io/telco-network-cloud-drivers/best-practices/demos/cicd-pipeline/</guid><description>Objectives This working demonstration showcases Telco Network Cloud Orchestration (TNCO) automated CI/CD capabilities. The demo will show the following
Automated triggering of Network Service or VNF build from a Git project source change. Creation of a pre-production environment and all VNF or test dependencies required to run the updated Network Service. Automated behaviour testing of the updated Network Service On success the network service binary package is built with an appropriate version number and stored in Nexus Pre-requisites Have read the CI/CD Hub Introduction Working CI/CD Hub and TNCO environment Install local LMCTL Working Docker Environment to run VNFs Installing the Demo Clone the Telco Network Cloud Orchestration (TNCO) demo artifacts from GitHub to your local machine</description></item></channel></rss>