<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Themes on Telco Network Cloud Orchestration Learning Center</title><link>https://ibm.github.io/telco-network-cloud-drivers/user-guides/administration/configuration/themes/</link><description>Recent content in Themes on Telco Network Cloud Orchestration Learning Center</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://ibm.github.io/telco-network-cloud-drivers/user-guides/administration/configuration/themes/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Themes Overview</title><link>https://ibm.github.io/telco-network-cloud-drivers/user-guides/administration/configuration/themes/theme-overview/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ibm.github.io/telco-network-cloud-drivers/user-guides/administration/configuration/themes/theme-overview/</guid><description>Changing the look of the Telco Network Cloud Orchestration (TNCO) User Interface UI is supported via Theme Packages. A theme can be provided for each unique look that is needed for the TNCO UI.
Changing the Theme of the TNCO UI To change the theme of the UI you need to produce a theme.tar containing the necessary elements. The TAR should include a directory for each potential theme. Each theme is represented by a directory which should include the favicon, stylesheet and images to be used: +-- mytheme (change to your Theme name)
| +-- favicon.</description></item><item><title>Theme Installation</title><link>https://ibm.github.io/telco-network-cloud-drivers/user-guides/administration/configuration/themes/theme-installation/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ibm.github.io/telco-network-cloud-drivers/user-guides/administration/configuration/themes/theme-installation/</guid><description>The following steps explain how to alter the installation process to change the theme used by the Telco Network Cloud Orchestration (TNCO) User Interface.
Installing a Theme Follow the steps in theme overview before doing the following.
When installing the lm-configurator helm chart you must include the following values, changing the value of theme.name to be the name of theme to be used:
configurator:
lmConfigImport:
nimrod:
alm.</description></item><item><title>Theme Updates</title><link>https://ibm.github.io/telco-network-cloud-drivers/user-guides/administration/configuration/themes/theme-running/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ibm.github.io/telco-network-cloud-drivers/user-guides/administration/configuration/themes/theme-running/</guid><description>The following steps explain how to change the theme used by the Telco Network Cloud Orchestration (TNCO) User Interface when it is running.
Updating a Theme Follow the steps in theme overview before doing the following.
Add the following configuration to vault for lm/nimrod, changing the value of theme.name to be the name of the theme to be used:
&amp;quot;alm.nimrod.theme.name&amp;quot;: &amp;quot;mytheme&amp;quot;
Create a values file with the following configuration: nimrod:
app:
config:
themesConfigMap: lm-themes
Run a helm upgrade of the TNCO helm chart with the custom values file above.</description></item></channel></rss>