<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Ansible-RM on Telco Network Cloud Orchestration Learning Center</title><link>https://ibm.github.io/telco-network-cloud-drivers/installation/resource-manager/ansible-rm/</link><description>Recent content in Ansible-RM on Telco Network Cloud Orchestration Learning Center</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://ibm.github.io/telco-network-cloud-drivers/installation/resource-manager/ansible-rm/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Getting Started</title><link>https://ibm.github.io/telco-network-cloud-drivers/installation/resource-manager/ansible-rm/ansible-rm-start/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ibm.github.io/telco-network-cloud-drivers/installation/resource-manager/ansible-rm/ansible-rm-start/</guid><description>This section details a recommended installation of the IBM OSSLM Ansible Resource Manager.
Pre-requisites Kubernetes A Kubernetes cluster is required to install the Ansible RM. This environment must be configured with:
a Storage Class to provision persistent volumes in your cluster a Namespace to install into (you may use the default) In addition, you will need the following client tools, pre-configured with access to your Kubernetes environment:
Helm kubectl Agile Lifecycle Manager (ALM) We recommend installing a ALM environment first so the Ansible RM may share the existing Kafka cluster.</description></item><item><title>Storage</title><link>https://ibm.github.io/telco-network-cloud-drivers/installation/resource-manager/ansible-rm/storage/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ibm.github.io/telco-network-cloud-drivers/installation/resource-manager/ansible-rm/storage/</guid><description>Existing Storage Services Ansible RM requires a connection to Cassandra and Kafka. By default the Helm chart is configured to locate existing persisted services using labels:
Cassandra - expects a Cassandra service in the same namespace with labels app=cassandra and release=foundation Kafka - expects a Kafka service in the same namespace with labels app=kafka and release=foundation Check your existing Cassandra and Kafka have the given labels. If you did not install foundation services from Agile Lifecycle Manager (ALM) with the Helm release name of foundation, then the release label may have an alternative value.</description></item><item><title>Access Configuration</title><link>https://ibm.github.io/telco-network-cloud-drivers/installation/resource-manager/ansible-rm/access-config/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ibm.github.io/telco-network-cloud-drivers/installation/resource-manager/ansible-rm/access-config/</guid><description>Hostnames and Ports The Ansible RM is configured to allow access through NodePorts. The default values for the HTTP and HTTPS ports are shown below. Override any defaults by adding them to your custom values.
service:
nodePort: 31080
sslNodePort: 31081
Next Steps You may now complete your installation of the Ansible RM</description></item><item><title>Install</title><link>https://ibm.github.io/telco-network-cloud-drivers/installation/resource-manager/ansible-rm/install-ansible-rm/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ibm.github.io/telco-network-cloud-drivers/installation/resource-manager/ansible-rm/install-ansible-rm/</guid><description>This section assumes you have followed the configuration steps and now have:
an Ansible RM Helm chart a custom values YAML file a target Kubernetes namespace with Agile Lifecycle Manager (ALM) installed Installing with Helm Install the Ansible RM with the helm install command.
helm install &amp;lt;ansible-rm-helm-chart&amp;gt; --name &amp;lt;your-release-name&amp;gt; --namespace &amp;lt;your-namespace&amp;gt; -f &amp;lt;your-custom-values-file&amp;gt;
ansible-rm-helm-chart - path to the Ansible RM Helm chart your-release-name - unique name used to identify this installation in Helm your-namespace - Kubernetes namespace with LM already installed your-custom-values-file - path to the YAML file created with any configuration overrides (if you have any) For example:</description></item></channel></rss>