<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Pipeline on Telco Network Cloud Orchestration Learning Center</title><link>/user-guides/cicd/pipeline/</link><description>Recent content in Pipeline on Telco Network Cloud Orchestration Learning Center</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="/user-guides/cicd/pipeline/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Create CI Pipeline</title><link>/user-guides/cicd/pipeline/create-ci-pipeline/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/user-guides/cicd/pipeline/create-ci-pipeline/</guid><description>Objectives Create a continuous integration (CI) pipeline that will automatically build and test VNF or Network Service packages when changes are detected in Git projects. This CI pipeline will be triggered when there is a check-in to the master branch of the VNF or Network Service git project.
Pre-requisites All VNF and Network Services packages the VNF or Network Service project under development depends on for both testing and when it is released.</description></item><item><title>Create Release Pipeline</title><link>/user-guides/cicd/pipeline/create-release-pipeline/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/user-guides/cicd/pipeline/create-release-pipeline/</guid><description>Objectives Create a release pipeline that will package a VNF or Network Service project into a binary package.
Pre-requisites CI Pipeline has already been configured and tested. Introduction This pipeline will be triggered when there is a check-in to the master branch. It will:
Checkout the project (tagged version) Check that all packages this project depends on in release have also been released (i.e. not SNAPSHOT versions) Check this version of the project has not already been released Rename the package in nexus (remove the SNAPSHOT) If the project is a NS, then deploy it&amp;rsquo;s package, and all the packages it depends on for release to the production TNCO.</description></item></channel></rss>