<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Developing a Project on Lifecycle Manager Learning Center</title><link>https://pages.github.ibm.com/TNC/alm-docs.github.io/user-guides/cicd/developing-a-project/</link><description>Recent content in Developing a Project on Lifecycle Manager Learning Center</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://pages.github.ibm.com/TNC/alm-docs.github.io/user-guides/cicd/developing-a-project/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Create New Project</title><link>https://pages.github.ibm.com/TNC/alm-docs.github.io/user-guides/cicd/developing-a-project/create-new-vnf-project/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://pages.github.ibm.com/TNC/alm-docs.github.io/user-guides/cicd/developing-a-project/create-new-vnf-project/</guid><description>Objectives Create a new VNF or Network Service project that will hold all of its descriptor, test and lifecycle script artifacts.
Pre-requisites Access to a CI/CD Hub and a development environment with a Lifecycle Manager and VIM
Design details of the new VNF or Network Service.
VNFCs or VNFs it will contain (name and version)
Software Images associated with each VNFC. (There may be multiple images for each target VIM type, e.</description></item><item><title>Uploading Images</title><link>https://pages.github.ibm.com/TNC/alm-docs.github.io/user-guides/cicd/developing-a-project/upload-images/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://pages.github.ibm.com/TNC/alm-docs.github.io/user-guides/cicd/developing-a-project/upload-images/</guid><description>Objectives Manage versions of all VNF or test software images in a general repository. Making the images available in a formal manner to the CI/CD tools.
Pre-requisites You are provided with the software images to upload on your local machine. Repository Structure The image directory structure in the CI/CD nexus general repository is as follows:
.
├── raw
└── vdus
└── &amp;lt;vdu-name&amp;gt;
├── &amp;lt;image-name-version&amp;gt;.&amp;lt;type&amp;gt;
├── image-3.4.12.qcow2
├── image-3.4.00.tar To upload an image into nexus:</description></item><item><title>Developing a Package</title><link>https://pages.github.ibm.com/TNC/alm-docs.github.io/user-guides/cicd/developing-a-project/developing-new-vnf/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://pages.github.ibm.com/TNC/alm-docs.github.io/user-guides/cicd/developing-a-project/developing-new-vnf/</guid><description>Objectives Develop VNF or Network Service project artifacts that, when complete, will constitute a releasable package.
Pre-requisites CI/CD Hub and a development environment with a dedicated Agile Lifecycle Manager (ALM) and VIM A VNF or Network Service project already exists. Developing a VNF or Network Service Descriptor Push your project into dev environment (assume this is called &amp;lsquo;dev&amp;rsquo; in the LMCONFIG file for LMCTL):
$ cd &amp;lt;myvnf dir&amp;gt;
$ lmctl project push dev
Design the VNF or Network Service Descriptor</description></item><item><title>Releasing a package</title><link>https://pages.github.ibm.com/TNC/alm-docs.github.io/user-guides/cicd/developing-a-project/release-package/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://pages.github.ibm.com/TNC/alm-docs.github.io/user-guides/cicd/developing-a-project/release-package/</guid><description>Objectives Release a VNF or Network Service package that has been confirmed ready for production use to a production environment
Pre-requisites The VNF or Network Service package is available in the Nexus general repository and marked ready for production deployment. Introduction When a package has been developed and its been agreed that it has been fully tested by its stakeholders, it can be released.
Releasing a VNF or Network Service package is done by triggering the Release pipeline job manually in Jenkins and giving the version of the package to deploy.</description></item><item><title>Add Tests to Package</title><link>https://pages.github.ibm.com/TNC/alm-docs.github.io/user-guides/cicd/developing-a-project/add-tests-to-package/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://pages.github.ibm.com/TNC/alm-docs.github.io/user-guides/cicd/developing-a-project/add-tests-to-package/</guid><description>Objectives This section shows how to add VNF functional behaviour tests or Network Service performance and interoperability test artifacts to your project structure in the CI/CD Hub.
Pre-requisites Development VIM and CI/CD Hub and ALM up and running LMCTL setup on your local machine with a profile configured for the above development environment VNF design documenting how test scenarios are expected to be run and the metrics and behaviour from all participating VNFs that constitute a successful test run.</description></item><item><title>Updating a package</title><link>https://pages.github.ibm.com/TNC/alm-docs.github.io/user-guides/cicd/developing-a-project/update-package/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://pages.github.ibm.com/TNC/alm-docs.github.io/user-guides/cicd/developing-a-project/update-package/</guid><description>Objectives Update a VNF or NS Project after Release
One a version of a project has been packaged and released it cannot be updated. A new version must be created and tested.
Pre-requisites Existing package
New package
Update Project to next version In the case where you want to update the last version:
Checkout the project on the develop branch Edit the projects descriptor (VNF or NS) to increment the version Edit the the Behaviour test template for the NS or VNF being tested to the new version make changes to your project for the update.</description></item></channel></rss>