<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Reference on Telco Network Cloud Orchestration Learning Center</title><link>/reference/</link><description>Recent content in Reference on Telco Network Cloud Orchestration Learning Center</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="/reference/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>CI/CD Hub Software Overview</title><link>/reference/cicdhub-software/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/reference/cicdhub-software/</guid><description>CI/CD Hub The CI/CD Hub is a reference deployment of a best practice suite of Continuous Integration and Continuous Delivery (CI/CD) tools. These collectively providing an infrastructure for Assembly and Resource package and descriptor development, release and distribution management. It leverages common, open source, third party tools augmenting Agile Lifecycle Manager (ALM) specific tools to enable an integration with one or more ALM instances as part of a holistic CI/CD environment.</description></item><item><title>Deployment Model</title><link>/reference/deployment-model/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/reference/deployment-model/</guid><description>Introduction This section introduces the deployment architecture and main configuration options for Agile Lifecycle Manager (ALM) for a typical CI/CD configuration. It is expected that multiple ALMs will be deployed to automate the various tasks for each stage of the CI/CD process. Each set of LMs are coordinated around a repository of artifacts representing the external resources under management. The picture below shows a typical deployment. See here for more information on a typical LM CI/CD process.</description></item><item><title>Glossary of Terms</title><link>/reference/glossary/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/reference/glossary/</guid><description>Agile Lifecycle Manager (ALM) uses a number of terms which have very specific meaning in its context. In some cases these terms are used in other products or industries to mean slightly different things. It is important that the user understand these terms in the context of ALM
Assembly Assembly is a definition of a service and may comprise of one or more resources and/or other assemblies. It is defined in an Assembly Descriptor and can be instantiated as an Assembly Instance.</description></item><item><title>ICP Advice</title><link>/reference/icp-pre-install/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/reference/icp-pre-install/</guid><description>ICP Pre-Install Considerations This section details topics that should be considered when installing the CI/CD Hub and/or Agile Lifecycle Manager (ALM) to ICP.
Helm Install the Helm client using the ICP instructions.
Pod Security Policy If you are installing CI/CD Hub or Agile Lifecycle Manager (ALM) on ICP, you should do so in a namespace that is bound to a less restrictive Pod Security Policy. We recommend creating a new namespace and binding it to an existing policy called ibm-anyuid-psp.</description></item><item><title>Lifecycle Manager Architecture</title><link>/reference/stratoss-lm-software-architecture/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/reference/stratoss-lm-software-architecture/</guid><description>Overview Agile Lifecycle Manager (ALM) software application is deployed as separated distinct component sets which can be considered in two groups;
Core ALM consisting of a number of microservices Dependencies: Foundation functionality consisting of industry standard third party implementations Message Bus Data Persistence Authentication Server ALM Core Microservices The ALM microservices are namely:
User Interface Host for ALM User Interface. API Gateway A gateway for the full set of published ALM APIs used by the ALM User Interface and available for use by any number of configured Client applications.</description></item><item><title>Lifecycle Manager Architecture -- State Models</title><link>/reference/state-models/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/reference/state-models/</guid><description>Component State Model Assemblies and resources have a predefined state model (comparable to TOSCA) as defined in the diagram below.
Components flow through this state model by performing lifecycle transitions. Resources can define which transitions they support (in their descriptors) but an assembly will always transition through
In addition to the five transitions shown below, resources can implement the Integrity transition, representing a functional “smoke test” which is performed prior to the resource becoming Active and after the Start Lifecycle Transition</description></item><item><title>LMCTL</title><link>/reference/lmctl/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/reference/lmctl/</guid><description>LMCTL is a command-line client for the Agile Lifecycle Manager (ALM) that provides commands for interacting with LM environments. It includes an opinionated pattern for managing service designs during the CI/CD lifecycle as projects, to produce packages suitable for release into production.
Please use version 2.5.0 of the LMCTL documentation with 2.2.0 of ALM.
lmctl - LM version compatibility:
LM Version lmctl Version 2.</description></item><item><title>Sizing your deployment</title><link>/reference/sizing-guidelines/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/reference/sizing-guidelines/</guid><description>Sizing guideline for ICP This guideline is for hardware requirements of installing Lifecycle Manager on top of IBM Cloud Private
Then, download the Agile Lifecycle Manager (ALM) sizing guideline from the attachment of this page. You will need Microsoft Excel to open this file.
Put your ICP cluster hardware details, and the desired number of resources you plan for ALM (assuming standard daily lifecycle actions). Make sure there&amp;rsquo;s enough hardware resources for your case.</description></item></channel></rss>